latinteenpass.com 2016-06-24

# Pacino Network Support

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our dedication to respecting privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.  

Non-Personal Information and Cookies

Certain non-personal information may be collected from visitors to this Site including, but not limited to, their browser type, operating system, IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the Site. Other non-personal information may be collected such as browsing behavior, date and time of visit, the pages visited; the time spent viewing the Site, the number of times the visitor returns to the Site, and click-stream data. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our Site. We may use cookies to collect this information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Site. You are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Site.  

Use of Information

This site automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. We may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, we does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.  
Security

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. As for all other information, visitors and subscribers should consider this communication and information to be non-confidential, and consequently, we assume no responsibility or liability if any information relating to any visitor or subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.  

Acceptance of these Terms

By visiting or subscribing to this Site, you agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may at any time revise or amend any of these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies which may collect personal information as a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the Site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Site may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
